<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CONVERGENCE</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string name="nav_item_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_item_friends">Friends</string>
    <string name="nav_item_notifications">Messages</string>

    <!-- navigation drawer item labels  -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_labels">
        <item>@string/nav_item_home</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_friends</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_notifications</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="title_friends">Friends</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="sportsdetails"><u><b><i><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></i></b></u>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Only team entries are eligible.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;A team shall consist of maximum two persons.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;The decision of the QUIZ MASTER will be final and will not be subjected to any change.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;The participants shall not be allowed to use MOBILE or OTHER ELECTRONIC INSTRUMENTS.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;The questions shall be in form of MULTIPLE CHOICE, VISUAL &amp; BRAIN TEASERS questions etc.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Audience shall not give any hints or clues to the participants.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Replacement of any participants of a team is not allowed after registration.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;29 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;11:00 AM To 12:00 Noon\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>CS EXAMINATION HALL\n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;Shitansu Pandey\n\n<b><u>VOLUNTEER</u>:-</b>&#160;Shiva Dubey\n\n</string>

    <string name="text">With the success of two intra college fests, Sir Chhotu Ram Institute of Engineering and Technology, is now on its way to organize and host, west u.p.’s biggest ever, inter college fest, “convergence’16” @ convergence’16, we aim at encouraging the young talent to exbhibit and exchange their innovative ideas and skills through varied activities covering quizzing, extempore, dance, drama, music, fashion, fine arts, et al. it also features a varied range of fun events like ad mad, battle of bands, lan gaming, treasure hunt, that are sure to give you a euphoric high
ALL IN ALL, IT NOT ONLY GIVES U A HUGE AMOUNT OF EXPERIENCE BUT ALSO SERVES AS A PEDESTIAL TO PATH OF GLORY BY ENABLING THE STUDENTS TO SET A BENCHMARK IN THE ENGINEERING REVOLUTION. </string>


    <string-array name="navDrawerItems">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Events</item>
        <item>Gallery</item>
        <item>Register</item>
        <item>Sponsors</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="navDrawerIcons">

        <item>@drawable/aboutrsz</item>
        <item>@drawable/eventsrsz</item>
        <item>@drawable/galleryrsz</item>
        <item>@drawable/registerrsz</item>
        <item>@drawable/sponsor</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="Technical">
        <item>LAN Gaming (NFS &amp; CS)</item>
        <item>Sports Quiz</item>
        <item>Technical Quiz</item>
        <item>General Quiz</item>
        <item>PPT Competition</item>
        <item>Model Making</item>
        <item>Code Hunt</item>
        <item>Best Out Of Waste</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Arts">
        <item>Poster Making</item>
        <item>Designing</item>
        <item>Painting/Sketching</item>
        <item>Rangoli</item>
        <item>Grafity</item>
        <item>Street Painting</item>
        <item>Face Painting</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Cultural">
        <item>Singing</item>
        <item>Dancing</item>
        <item>Instrumental</item>
        <item>Battle Of Bands</item>
        <item>Photography</item>
        <item>Street Play</item>
        <item>Stage Play</item>
        <item>Dramatics</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Oratory">
        <item>Extempore</item>
        <item>Debate</item>
        <item>Poetry</item>
        <item>Speech</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="pptdetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;All the participants are allowed to use a maximum of 15 slides in their PowerPoint presentation.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;The participants should make your Title headlines, Not descriptions or else the marks are reduced . For Example :- Population Growth
(Description) / Population grow by 40% (Headline)\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;The titles Used by The participants must tell the topics. ( Non topic titles are not allowed in the P.P.T )\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;The presenter must use the proper language skills to make the audience and judges to get the theme correctly and clearly. It can be in
Both Hindi and English ( Probably English is preferred more )\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;The participant is asked to bring their P.P.T file slides in the DVD’s and pen drives so that in the case of emergency or data loss it can be
used to show your presentation slides. Or else you are allowed to carry your own laptops to show your own P.P.T slides.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;The participant should have a proper dress up and body language , any vulgar behavior is not at all tolerated. If anybody was found doing
that his/her name is removed from he participant list.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;The participant must complete his/her presentation in the allotted time period only as per rules. No extra time is given and no excuses are
heard.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;The participant should give their names with the topic of presentation to the event In charge by one week before the event.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;The participant should be present in the event venue, a hour before it was started over. And was allowed to give presentation at the time
of his/her turn only.\n\n<b>10.</b>&#160;All the audiences are asked to “KEEP PIN DROP SILENCE” in the presentation room. It may directly or indirectly effect the participants
performance. (If anybody is found doing nuisance activity will be sent out of the room immediately.)\n\n<b>11.</b>&#160;The maximum time limit provided to each participant is 10 min. If the participant needs laser light and scale for highlighting points
he/she should get these by themselves none of these items are provided by us.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;29 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;11:00 AM To 12:00 Noon\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>CS HALL\n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;Sourabh Pal,Shweta\n\n<b><u>VOLUNTEER</u>:-</b>&#160;Aditi Awasthi,Saurabh Saxena,Pragyan Kumar\n\n</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="modeldetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Maximum 5 members are allowed in one team.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;At least one member to describe &amp; for discussing on their model.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160; Discipline must be maintain in campus.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;No harmful &amp; flmable things are allowed in model.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Decision of judges are final &amp; no one can challenge the judgment.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Maintain a file related to their model in which they show all details , theory &amp; advantage of model etc.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Model will submit before 29th april 2016.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;The model have 2 types\n<b>(i)</b>&#160;Working Model.\n<b>(ii)</b>&#160;Non Working Model.\n\n Working model must be in working condition at the time of examing.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;29 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;11:00 AM To 12:00 Noon\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>ME Dept\n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;Rahul Yadav , Javed , Dhirender\n\n<b><u>VOLUNTEER</u>:-</b>&#160;Akash ,Bharat , Prashant\n\n</string>

    <string name="codehuntdetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;The duration of the event will be 2 hours.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;The event consist in 2 round.First round is multiple type question.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Second round is C language Coding Problem Solving.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;The member will write codes for solving some of the trickiest c"-"language coding problems .\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Mobiles and calculator is not allowed.Member can not interact with each other after the event start.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;30 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;10:00 AM To 12:00 Noon\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>CS LAB\n\n<b><u>CORE MEMBER</u>:-</b>&#160;Abhishek , Vishal \n\n<b><u>Co-ordinator</u>:-</b>&#160;Rajvee gupta &amp; krishna\n\n</string>
    <string name="cvg"><b><i>CONVERGENCE 16</i></b></string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="singingdetail"><b>*</b>&#160;The organizing Committee reserves the right to change the venue,time and rules, if desired.\n\n<b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;The Singing Competition in Two Categories and Result of all two Categories to beannounced separately.\n&#160;<u><b>Categories are</b></u>:-\n(i)&#160;Solo\n(ii)&#160;Dual or Group\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;The event consist of 2 round:-\n(i)&#160;Audition Round .\n(ii)Final Round. \n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;The Time Limit is 3 minutes for solo singing and 5 minute for duet or group singing.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;If the timing of the performance will be over the given time then we will stop your performance.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Registration is Available ONLINE ON convergence application AND OFFLINE FORM.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Certificate will be given to all final participants.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Participant must bring their song’s Karaoke or Musical instrument.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;Every Participant must bring their College ID card with them, without ID card Participant is not allowed to Participate.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;The song must not include any Objectionable Word or Non-Acceptable Word.\n\n<b>10.</b>&#160;The Performance (Song) should be Theme Based.(Ex: Classical / Semi-Classical / Folk / Patriotic / Motivational / Sibling love).\n\n<b>11.</b>&#160;The participant who is selected by the audition have to sing same song in finals, additionally he/she have to prepare 2 more song in case of judges demand.\n\n<b>12.</b>&#160;Announcement of the Short listed Candidates for the Final Round Will on the same day of Audition.\n\n <b>13.</b>&#160;Judges decision is final decision.\n\n<b><u><big>Theme</big></u>:-</b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Patriotism\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Inpirational\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Motivational\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Classical\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Sibilings love\n\n</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Coming Soon....</string>
    <string name="battleofbanddetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Interested performers must send their demo tracks in the form of digital mp3"'"s\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;The round of performances held on the day of the event is the final performance round.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Each bands shall have 15 minutes. The 15 minutes is inclusive of the time of performance alone.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;An extra 5"-"7 minutes will be given to the band to set up their equipment.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;There should not be any socially unacceptable lyrics .\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Failure to abide by this rule will result in immediate disqualification.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;If all members of your band are not present backstage 30 minutes priorto the time you are assigned to perform, your act will be disqualified.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;29 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;4 pm to 5:30 pm\n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>Gaurav Gautam(8869060390),Prabhat Kumar\n\n</string>
    <string name="intrumentaldetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Preliminary / Elimination round is a qualifying for the event. Those participants who fail to appear for the preliminary round shall not be considered for the finals.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;The maximum time allowed to each candidate is 6 minutes and 30sec for sound check.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;No pre­recorded Music or sample sound is allowed.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Organizing committee shall not provide any instruments/accompanists.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;The contestant may opt for a suitable dress code however the name of the college should not be displayed on the dresses in any form.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;The decision of Judges will be final and binding.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;The rules and regulations for the preliminary and final round shall remain the same.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;In case participants exceed the time limit Judges will be free to disqualify the participant.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160; The organizing Committee reserves the right to change the venue,time and rules, if desired.\n\n</string>

    <string name="paintingdetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Mobiles Banned.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Filling of entry form\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;No Material with Participant\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Maximum timing will be 1 hrs.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Single &amp;Double participation should allowed.\n\n<b><u>Date</u></b>:-&#160;29 April.\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>-&#160;11 am to 12 pm\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>&#160;Outer area of EC Seminar Hall.\n\n<b><u>CO"-"ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;Pinky\n\n</string>

    <string name="stageplaydetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Play should not be based on such issue which can hurt the feelings or emotions of anyone\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Maximum time limit is 15"-"20 min.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Script should be mailed by 21 st of may.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;In case if your play has background music then it should be provided 30 min before the event.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Negative points for exceeding the time limit.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Participants should report 30 min before the event.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>30 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>10 am to 1 pm\n\n<b><u>Co – ordinator</u></b>:-Pooja Yadav, Rahul Raghuvanshi(7860799991), Yavnika Soam\n\n</string>

    <string name="dramaticsdetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b><big>*</big></b>&#160;Dramatics include"-"Mono acting,mime&amp;mimicry\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Mime mook abhinaya is acting without words.It is an act which expresses through gestures,postures, and facial expressions. It portrays ideas, themes or tells the story through body language only.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Maximum no. of participants in a team is 6.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Maximum time allotted for each act is 4-5 min.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Negative marking for exceeding the time limit .\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Participants should reach 30 min before the competition .\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Props will be brought up by the participants.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Make sure that your act does not hurt the feelings or emotions of anyone.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;Judgement will most likely be based on qualities like idea ,creativity of presentation,use of make-up,costume ,music and general impression .\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;As you are performing on a college fest no any improper or obsessive language or posture or act should be performed.\n\n<b>10.</b>&#160;The background music on which you are performing must provide that in pen drive 30min before the event starts.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>30 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>10 am to 1 pm\n\n<b><u>Co – ordinator</u></b>:-Pooja Yadav, Rahul Raghuvanshi(7860799991), Yavnika Soam\n\n</string>
    <string name="speechdetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;The maximum time will be three minutes only for speech.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Language may be &quot;English&quot; or&quot; Hindi&quot;.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;The negative marking will be considered if a participant takes more than three minutes for speech.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Bell will be rung at 2:30min for the indication of time.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Participant can switch the language as &quot;English&quot; to&quot;Hindi&quot; or &quot; Hindi&quot; to &quot;English&quot;.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;The topic of the speech will be pre-decided.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Speech must be original.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;Participant must not identify themselves in anyway, by name or by college.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;No microphones are permitted for the participant during the speech.\n\n<b>10.</b>&#160;Notes on card for the reference are not permitted.\n\n<b>11.</b>&#160;The objectionable remark are not permitted in the speech.\n\n<b>12.</b>&#160;Every participant must bring their College ID card with them, with out id card participant is not allowed to participate.\n\n<b>13.</b>&#160;No entry fee.\n\n<b>14.</b>&#160;Decision of the judge shell be final.\n\n<b><u>Topic</u>:-</b><b>Gravity of water shortage at national level</b>\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;30 april 16.\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;10.00 am to 1.00 pm\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>EC Seminar hall \n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;Chandraveer\n\n</string>

    <string name="facepaintingdetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;It is a team event there can only 2 participants in a team.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Time limit is 60 mins.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Topic will be given on the spot.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Participants will be judge on the basis of creativity , innovation and design.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Decision of judges will be final &amp; binding.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;29 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;11:00 AM To 12:00 Noon\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>Outer area of EC Seminar Hall.\n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;Jigyasa \n\n<b><u>VOLUNTEER</u>:-</b>&#160;Ashutosh Rao\n\n</string>

    <string name="generalquiz"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Only team enteries are allowed.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;A team shall consist of two person.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;The decision of the quiz master will be final and will NOT be subjected to any change.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;The participants shall NOT be allowed to use mobile or any other electronic device.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Audience shall NOT give any hints or clues to the competitors.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;If any team uses unfair means , it would be immediately disqualified from the competition.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Repalcement of any participant of a team is NOT allowed after registration.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;29 april 16.\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;1 pm to 2 pm \n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>EC Seminar hall \n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;MONIKA GUPTA , NIDHI SAXENA\n\n<b><u>VOLUNTEER</u>:-</b>&#160;NATWAR SINH(8864813647)\n\n</string>
     <string name="technicalquiz"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Only team enteries are allowed.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;A team shall consist of two person.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;The decision of the quiz master will be final and will NOT be subjected to any change.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;The participants shall NOT be allowed to use mobile or any other electronic device.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Audience shall NOT give any hints or clues to the competitors.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;If any team uses unfair means , it would be immediately disqualified from the competition.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Repalcement of any participant of a team is NOT allowed after registration.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;29 april 16.\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;10.00 am to 1.00 pm\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>EC Seminar hall \n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;Satyendra\n\n<b><u>VOLUNTEER</u>:-</b>&#160;Mudit\n\n</string>
    <string name="posterdetails"><b><big><u>POSTER MAKING ON FEMALE FEOTISIDE.</u></big></b></string>
    <string name="rangolidetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Single and double participation should allowed.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Maximum timing should one hour.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Rangoli should be clean and attractive.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Rangoli should be in 3 feet area.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Mobiles and any type of picture are not allowed.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;29 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;11:00 AM To 12:00 Noon\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>Outer area of EC Seminar Hall.\n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;Neha Katiyar\n\n<b><u>VOLUNTEER</u>:-</b>&#160;Deeksha Chaturvedi ,Manish kumar Mandal\n\n</string>

    <string name="debatedetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;The language of communication should be any ENGLISH/ HINDI (BOTH) only content is important.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Registration will be done before 1 hour of the event.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Participants are divided into groups. In each groups two members are there.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;One member is speak for the motion &amp; another memberis speak against the motion.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Only 5 min is allotted to each group : 2 min for each member of a group &amp; 1 min for rebuttal.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;A warning bell will be given at the end of 1.5 minutes.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Speech notes are not to be used by the contestant while presenting his/her speech.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;Decision of judges will be considered final.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;Discipline is of prime importance.\n\n<b><u>TIME LIMIT</u>:-</b>&#160;2 Min.\n\n<b><u>NO. OF MEMBER IN A GROUP</u>:-</b>&#160;2 member (for and against )\n\n<b><u>Topic</u>:-</b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;"Future of Nuclear Energy in the service of mankind" will it replace the existing sources<b>\n\n<u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;30 April.\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;11:00 AM TO 12:00 Noon\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>&#160;EC seminar hall, ground floor\n\n<b><u>Co – ordinator</u>:-</b>&#160;RASHMI RUPAM\n\n<b><u>Volunteer</u>:-</b>&#160;DIKSHA CHATURVEDI\n\n</string>
    <string name="extemporedetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;The language of communication should be any thing ENGLISH or HINDI or both only content is important.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Registration will be done before 1 hour of the event.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Only 3 min will be allotted to each contestant : 2 minfor speaking &amp; 1 min for preparing .\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;The topic will be given ON THE SPOT .\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;The speech should includes a brief introduction of the participant.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;A warning bell will be given at the end of 1.5 min.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Speech notes are not to be used by the contestant while presenting his/her speech.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;Second round will be conducted in case of tie of winning or runner-up position.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;Participants must carry their own pens.\n\n<b>10.</b>&#160;Decision of judges will be considered final.\n\n<b>11.</b>&#160;Discipline in of prime importance .\n\n<b><u>TOPIC</u>:-</b>&#160;ON THE SPOT.\n\n<b><u>TIME LIMIT</u>:-</b>&#160;2 min\n\n<b><u>DATE</u>:-</b>&#160;30 April\n\n<b><u>TIME</u>:-</b>&#160;12:00 Noon to 1:00 P.M\n\n<b><u>VENUE</u>:-</b>&#160;EC Seminar Hall , Ground floor\n\n<b><u>Co"–"ordinator</u>:-</b>&#160;RASHMI RUPAM\n\n<b><u>Volunteer</u>:-</b>&#160;DIKSHA CHATURVEDI\n\n</string>
    <string name="titlesponser"><b><u><big>TITLE SPONSOR</big></u></b></string>
    <string name="eventsponsor"><b><u><big>EVENT SPONSOR</big></u></b></string>

    <string name="poetrydetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Poetry should be self written and should be submitted before recitation.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Maximum time limit is 4 min for reciatation.Extra time will lead to negative marking.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;No objectional wording and expression should be used.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Participations have to pass the cutoff round.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Failure to complete the poem wiill result disqualification.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Theme of the Poetry will be declared on Spot .\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Decision of Judges will be final.\n\n</string>

    <string name="dancingdetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b><u><big>Solo Dance</big></u></b>\n\nThe fight for individual glory in dance as never seen before. Introduced for the first time in SCRIET CCS University Meerut, the solo dance event took off with outstanding levels of participation and an enthusiastic reception.\n\n<b><u><big>General Rules:</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Participants should get their songs/music on a CD or a pen"-"drive. It is advised that they have a back"-"up in a CD. Team dance Fest will not be responsible for this.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Live music is not allowed.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;The participating teams are requested to ensure that their presentation in both audition and finals will be same and the performance is in keeping with the dignity of the fest.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Accessories, costumes, props will have to be arranged by the participants.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Any type of vulgarity through dance is not allowed.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;The performance should be in cohesion with the integrity of the fest.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;The decision of the judges and the organizing team will be final and binding.\n\n<b><u><big>Audition:</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;The audition will be conducted on 22 April 2016.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;This is an individual event.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Time limit is 1.5min"-"2 min.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Judging criteria includes choreography, stage utilization, energy level, innovation, presentation, and overall impact on the crowd.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;For the audition, individuals need to submit their song track through Pendrive/CD.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;The maximum length of the submission should not exceed 2 minutes.\n\n<b><u><big>Finals:</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;The finals will be conducted in Open Stage during the fest.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Shortlisted participants in audition shall be eligible for final round.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Time limit is 2.5 min "-" 3 min.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Judging criteria":" Choreography"-" 35 percent Justification with given emotion "-" 20 percent Attitude"-" 20 percent Stage Utilization"-" 15 percent Crowd Response"-" 10 percent\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;For both audition and finals, 20 percent marks will be deducted if the performance exceeds by 10sec.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;If the performance increases further by 20 sec, it will lead to disqualification.\n\n<b><u><big>Group Dance:</big></u></b>\n\nAn inter"-"collegiate dance competition, Centrifuge is a stage frequented by best dance groups. With no restrictions on genre, Centrifuge witnesses participants flaunting their dance moves in styles ranging from kathakali to contemporary.With the focus on co"-"ordination, choreography and technique, Centrifuge promises to be an event to test your skills like no other.\n\n<b><u><big>RULES :</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;This is an inter"-"collegiate event and there shall be only one team representing our college in, comprising of minimum 4 active members.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;The time limit of the performance will be 5 minutes.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Marks shall be deducted for exceeding the time limit 20percent deducted for exceeding 10 minutes and team might be disqualified for exceeding 12 minutes based on the judge"'"s discretion.\n\n<b><u><big>General Rules:</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Participants should get their songs/music on a CD and a pen"-"drive. It is advised that they have a back-up in a CD. Team of Fest will not be responsible for this.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Live music is not allowed.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;The performance is in keeping with the dignity of the fest.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Use of any obscene language in music tracks is strictly prohibited.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Accessories, costumes have to be arranged by participants.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Any type of vulgarity through dance not allowed.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;The performance should be in cohesion with the integrity of the fest.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;The decision of the judges and the organizing team will be final and binding.\n\n<b><u><big>Theme</big></u>:-</b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Patriotism\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Inpirational\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Motivational\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Classical\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Sibilings love\n\n</string>
    <string name="bestoutofbestdetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;There must be proper registration, call details about you &amp; what are you going to make.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Participation can be in form of group &amp; solo as well.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Groups limits are Minimun 2 &amp; Maximun upto 10 members in a group.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Maximum 90 minutes will be provided to present your work.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Basic stationary will be provived.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Participants will have to bring their own waste materials.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Partipants cannot copy from other participants.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;The judge"'"s decision will be final &amp; cannot be questioned or challanged.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;Participants have to carry their registration slip &amp; college Id"-" card with them.\n\n<b>10.</b>&#160;Every work should be in discipline.\n\n</string>
    <string name="streetplaydetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Maximum number of participants is 15 allotted in a group.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Maximum time allotted for each act is 10"-"15 min.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Negative marking for exceeding the time limit.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Participants should reach 30 min before the competition.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Props should be brought up by the participants.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Make sure that your act doesn"’"t hurt feelings or emotions of others.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Final decision will be made by the jury panel.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>30 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>10 am to 1 pm\n\n<b><u>Co – ordinator</u></b>:-Pooja Yadav, Rahul Raghuvanshi(7860799991), Yavnika Soam\n\n</string>

    <string name="photographydetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;There is no limit for participants.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Each participant has to give only 4"-"5 photographs to present himself/herself.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;If you send the photographs to us that would be valid other shall not be conclude.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;The photographs may not be edited by any software.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Each photograph have must story. If you are selected in this event you have to explain what the photographs mean for you and why you took it?\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;If you can"’"t you will be disqualify.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;If any type of misbehavior, undisciplined are present, participant would be disqualified immediately.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;The decision of the judges will final.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;Last date of submission April 26, 2016 mid night.\n\n</string>
    <string name="langamingdetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b><u><big>GENERAL RULES:</big></u></b>\n\n<b>These rules apply to everyone attending. They can be changed without notice.</b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;You are responsible for your actions and equipment. We are not liable for anything that happens to you and your equipment.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Do not attempt to steal items from the event or anyone else. Legal consequences will be there.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Cheating is not tolerated.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Do not bring any type of hacks/viruses/etc. to the event.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Listen to those in charge.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;We reserve the right to remove anyone from premises for any reason we fit.\n\n<b><u><big>COUNTER STRIKE RULES:</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;1st round will be knife round.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;For the knife round. The winner of the knife round picks the side they want to play first(CT or T).\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Matches will be played 5 on 5.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;The map list for the tournament will be informed by the organizers on the day of tournament.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Automatic snipers(D3/Au"-"1,Krieg"-" 550), tactical shield, SG"-" 552, SG"-" 550, Scout, G3SG/1 are strictly not allowed.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;General rules settings:\n\n<b>(i)</b>&#160;Starting Money:$16,000\n\n<b>(ii)</b>&#160;Spectate is OFF, fade to block is ON.\n\n<b>(iii)</b>&#160;Map Time :3 minutes.\n\n<b>(iv)</b>&#160;C4 Timer:45 seconds.\n\n<b>(v)</b>&#160;Freeze Time:5 seconds\n\n<b>(vi)</b>&#160;Buy Time:30 seconds.\n\n<b>(vii)</b>&#160;Friendly Fire:OFF.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Team messages are allowed.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;If disconnection occurs during a match then scores till the last round will continue and starting money will be decided by the organizers.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;Playing with fewer than 5 players in any match is permitted with captain"’"s agreement.\n\n<b>10.</b>&#160;Under no circumstances are silent plants allowed; whether accidentally or intentionally.\n\n<b><u><big>NFS Most Wanted Competition Rules</big></u>:-</b>\n\nGame Version: NFS Most Wanted 1.3\n\nGeneral Competition Method: 4 players\n\n<b><u><big>Rules for Preliminaries:</big></u></b>\n\nGame Type : Circuit , Sprint.\n\nThe Circuit is for 2 rounds\n\nPlayers getting the 1st position shall qualify for the next round.\n\n<b><u><big>Rules for the tournament:</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;The tournament will be knock out.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;The player who wins their 1st stage match advances to the next stage.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;There will not be any match played for the third spot.\n\n<b><u><big>Game Settings</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;Courses: Course selection is done by the Game Admininstrator.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Car Settings: All cars are available.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Race Mode Options:\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Nitrous: On\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Collision Detection: oN\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Performance Matching: Off\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Units: Player"'"s own discretion\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160; Player Mode Options:\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Game Moment Camera: Off\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Car Damage: Off\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Rear View Mirror: Player"'"s own discretion.\n\n<b>5.</b>&#160;Players are provided with a standard keyboard and mouse. Other Controllers and Steering Wheel are allowed\n\n<b><u><big>Penalty for Unfair Play</big></u>:-</b>\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Unfair play\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Use of any cheat program.\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Intentional disconnection.\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Use of any settings exceeding standard and permitted settings.\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;If the match is disrupted due to unnecessary chatting, the player may be given a warning or lose by default at the referee"’"s sole discretion.\n\n <b>*</b>&#160;Upon discovery of any player committing any violations regarded as unfair play, that player will be disqualified from the Tournament/Preliminaries.\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;During the course of any match, the operations staff and/or referee may determine other actions to be unfair play at any time.\n\n<b>*</b>&#160;Two warnings constitute being disqualified from the Tournament/Preliminaries.\n\n<b><u>Date:-</u></b>&#160;29 April\n\n<b><u>Time:-</u></b>&#160;11 am to 3 pm\n\n<b><u>Venue</u>:-</b>&#160;Cs / It dept\n\n<b><u>CO-ORDINATOR</u>:-</b>&#160;Shivam kakkar\n,Arpit Malik(7037985849)\n,Ankit Singh\n\n</string>

    <string name="grafitydetails"><b><u><big>Rules &amp; Regulations:-</big></u></b>\n\n<b>1.</b>&#160;It is a team event. However, lone wolves (individuals) are welcome too.\n\n<b>2.</b>&#160;Teams from other institutes may also take part.\n\n<b>3.</b>&#160;Each entry should have a maximum of five (5) members.\n\n<b>4.</b>&#160;Registrations are open till 28th April 2016, after that no registrations will be accepted.<b>5.</b>&#160;Contestants are not allowed to use their mobiles or any cheating paper during the competition.\n\n<b>6.</b>&#160;Do not bite (copy) someone else work.\n\n<b>7.</b>&#160;Canvas / Wall, chalk will be provided.\n\n<b>8.</b>&#160;You are welcome to bring your own tools for convenience.\n\n<b>9.</b>&#160;All the contestants must complete their mural within 2 hours (2PM to 4PM).\n\n<b>10.</b>&#160;All graffiti must be completed on provided canvas.\n\n<b>11.</b>&#160;If any contestant misbehaves during the competition he/she will be disqualified.\n\n<b>12.</b>&#160;Decision by the judges is final. There is no appeal process. PROTEST"­" is prohibited.\n\n<b><u>Date</u>:-</b>&#160;29 April\n\n<b><u>Time</u>:-</b>&#160;2 pm to 4 pm\n\n<b><u>Co"–"ordinator</u>:-</b>&#160;Brilliance\n\n</string>
</resources>


